From your course dashboard, click the
Insights tab. This tab displays
cue-2
information about how students interact
with your content and assessments.
cue-3
Under the Content tab, you will see
student progress and proficiency levels
cue-4
organized by unit or module.
cue-5
This tells you in aggregate how far
students have progressed in a given
cue-6
section and their overall proficiency. You
can filter by searching unit names and
cue-7
selecting Student Progress or Student
Proficiency.
cue-8
In the Learning Objectives section, you
will find a proficiency breakdown
cue-9
organized by learning objectives. The
displayed analysis is based on the
cue-10
learning objectives you set. If your
course does not have learning objectives,
cue-11
no insights will appear. For example, this
course contains four learning objectives.
cue-12
When you hover on the proficiency
progress bar, the detailed data will show
cue-13
up for each objective. This breakdown
helps you understand where students are
cue-14
excelling and where they might need extra
support. You can also filter by module to
cue-15
check on specific parts of your course.
Under Scored Activities and Practice
cue-16
Activities, you will see the assessment
data of each unit on students' average
cue-17
scores, attempts and progress. For both of
the activities tab, you can dig into one
cue-18
unit by clicking on it, and the questions
breakdown would appear right below the
cue-19
table. This shows you how students are
performing on each question, including
cue-20
attempts at incorrect answer patterns.
cue-21
Note that anything you change here will
not be saved and updated to the course.
cue-22
Under the Surveys tab, you can click into
the page to see survey results if your
cue-23
course includes surveys. This is a great
place to check in on feedback or gather
cue-24
formative insights from your students.